Topical files 2
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Topical files 2, 2.1.9.5
  - George W. Hill, 1948 - 1949; 42 (Box 1617)
    - [George W. Hill:]Salesman, engineer, manufacturers agent, hunter, angler, hiker (on the A-Appalachian Trail) and skier - Therefore can appreciate very much, the comparisons and qualifications in the attached-&, 1
    - Verso: Salesman, engineer, manufacturers agent, hunter, angler, hiker (on the A-Appalachian Trail) and skier - Therefore can appreciate very much, the comparisons and qualifications in the attached-&, 1-verso
    - Note: [Memo from George W. Hill], 2
  - Lowell Hill, 1970; 43 (Box 1617)
    - Lowell Hill, Macon, Miss., 1
    - Verso: Lowell Hill, Macon, Miss., 1-verso
    - [Lowell Hill:]Note: The Senior Class of Noxubee County High School announces its Commencement Exercises Firday evening, May the twenty-second, eight o'clock, High School Gymnasium, 2
    - Note: [back of card], 3
  - George R. Hofman [color photograph], 1972; 44 (Box 1617)
    - [George R. Hoffman (color photograph): From the inside of a resturaunt looking out a window], 1
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 1 of letter to Lowell Thomas from George R. Hofman], 2
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 2 of letter to Lowell Thomas from George R. Hofman], 3
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 3 of letter to Lowell Thomas from George R. Hofman], 4
  - Maurice Holland [color photograph], 1972; 45 (Box 1617)
    - [Maurice Holland:]Caption: For Lowell Thomas, 1
    - Verso: [mostly illegible] M.I.T. Class 1916, 1-verso
    - Note[PDF]: [to Lowell Thomas from Maurice Holland, mostly illegible], 2
  - Homer H. Hoffaker, 1965 - 1972; 46 (Box 1617)
    - [Homer H. Hoffaker:]Homer and his dog, Toby, 1
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Homer H. and Geda[?] Hoffaker, 2
  - Dottie Horne [color photograph], 1973; 47 (Box 1617)
    - [Dottie Horne:]dudian[?]; Child at Rosebud [?] pow-wow '72 [?], 1
    - Verso: dudian[?]; Child at Rosebud [?] pow-wow '72 [?], 1-verso
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 1 of letter to Lowell Thomas from Dottie Horne], 2
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 2 of letter to Lowell Thomas from Dottie Horne], 3
  - George R. Hutchinson, 1975; 48 (Box 1617)
    - [George R. Hutchinson:]Note: Lowell Thomas, Personal&Important, 1
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from George R. Hutchinson], 2
    - [George R. Hutchinson:]World Wide C.B.S. radio broadcast from Rio-de-Janerio, Brazil, Hutchinson Family&1939, 3
    - [George R. Hutchinson:]Note: World Wide C.B.S. radio broadcast from Rio-de-Janerio, Brazil, Hutchinson Family&1939, 4
    - [George R. Hutchinson: Three women and a man standing in front of an airplane], 5
  - Betty W. Keenan [color photographs], 1974; 49 (Box 1617)
    - March 1975 Betty + Scott, Christmas 1974, Scott Keenan - Betty Keenan, 1
    - Verso: March 1975 Betty + Scott, Christmas 1974, Scott Keenan - Betty Keenan, 1-verso
    - March 1975 L to R Lois Wagner- Cindy Keenan Dower, Betty Wagner Kennan, 2
    - Verso: March 1975 L to R Lois Wagner- Cindy Keenan Dower, Betty Wagner Kennan, 2-verso
    - [Betty W. Keenan:]March 1975 Cindy, Paul + Buffy at Betty's Christmas 1974, 3
    - Verso: March 1975 Cindy, Paul + Buffy at Betty's Christmas 1974, 3-verso
    - [Betty W. Keenan:]March 1975 Scott + Lois Christmas 1974 Scott Keenan - Lois Wagner, 4
    - Verso: March 1975 Scott + Lois Christmas 1974 Scott Keenan - Lois Wagner, 4-verso
  - Joan Klein [color photograph], 1978; 50 (Box 1617)
    - Joan Klein 5th Grade North S. Greenville, O., 1
    - Verso: Joan Klein 5th Grade North S. Greenville, O., 1-verso
  - Roger Krupp, circa 1975; 51 (Box 1617)
    - Caption: To Lowell Thomas from one of his Old Announcers, Sincerely, Roger Krupp, Verso: Time has even weathered this picture., 1
    - Verso: Time has even weathered this picture., 1-verso
  - L - Miscellaneous, 1940 - 1949; 52 (Box 1617)
    - [L - Miscellaneous:]Caption: Edward Meluice, Clyde Levy[?], 1
    - [L - Miscellaneous:]Note: Souvenir of the Palms Bar, 2
    - [L - Miscellaneous:]Note: [reverse of note], 3
  - Francis Lamar, circa 1941; 53 (Box 1617)
    - [Francis Lamar: Shirtless man posing], 1
    - [Francis Lamar: Portrait of man], 2
    - [Francis Lamar: Picture of man's bare back, flexing], 3
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Francis Lamar], 4
  - George Lambros, Jr., 1959; 54 (Box 1617)
    - [George Lambros, Jr.:]Caption: 20th Century Fox - Dimond 2 9871 Lambros Air Charter, Ridgefield pk, N.J., 1
    - [George Lambros, Jr.:]Caption: Jam Handy Productions - Lambros Air Charter Ridgefield Pk, N.J. Dimond 2 9871, 2
    - [George Lambros, Jr.:]Caption: "Beau James" VistaVision Paramount Pictures, Lambros Aircharter Ridgefield Pk, N.J. Dimond 2 987I, 3
    - Verso: Lambros Air Charter Ridgefield PK-N.J. D1-2-9871 - DU4-7141 Res., 3-verso
    - Note[PDF]: [Letter 1 to Lowell Thomas from George Lambros, Jr,], 4
    - Note[PDF]: [Letter 2 to Lowell Thomas from George Lambros, Jr,], 5
  - Lancaster and Chester Railroad Company, 1970; 55 (Box 1617)
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from H.W. Close, President, Lancaster and Chester Railway Company, 1
    - [Lancaster and Chester Railroad Company: People sitting in a train, man playing the piano], 2
    - [Lancaster and Chester Railroad Company: Band playing, People standing on the caboose of the train], 3
  - Christine Larson [color photograph], circa 1960; 56 (Box 1617)
    - [Christine Larson (color photo):]Caption: To Lowell Thomas. Your Faithful Fan- Christine. 1920------1966., 1
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 1 of letter to Lowell Thomas from Christine Larson], 2
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 2 of letter to Lowell Thomas from Christine Larson], 3
  - Harry O. Lathum, circa 1949 - 1952; 57 (Box 1617)
    - [Harry O. Lathum:]Cabin on West Side of Hammersley Road opposite house., 1
    - Verso: Cabin on West Side of Hammersley Road opposite house., 1-verso
    - [Harry O. Lathum:]Clatterbrook, West side of house on Hammersley Road, 2
    - Verso: Clatterbrook, West side of house on Hammersley Road, 2-verso
    - [Harry O. Lathum:]Clatterbrook, Southwest view of house from Hammersley Road, 3
    - Verso: Clatterbrook, Southwest view of house from Hammersley Road, 3-verso
    - Note[PDF]: [Harry O. Lathum:]Note: [Page 1 of description of Clatterbrook], 4
    - Note[PDF]: [Harry O. Lathum:]Note: [Page 2 of description of Clatterbrook], 5
    - [Harry O. Lathum:]Latham's Home, So. Quaker Hill, Pawling, N.Y.; East side of vegetable garden with house in distance, 6
    - Verso: Latham's Home, So. Quaker Hill, Pawling, N.Y.; East side of vegetable garden with house in distance, 6-verso
    - [Harry O. Lathum:]Latham's Home, So. Quaker Hill, Pawling, N.Y.; The house from the Southeast, 7
    - Verso: Latham's Home, So. Quaker Hill, Pawling, N.Y.; The house from the Southeast, 7-verso
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 1 of description of Harry O. Latham Property], 8
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 2 of description of Harry O. Latham Property], 9
  - William O. Lau [color photographs], circa 1973 - 1976; 58 (Box 1617)
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from William O. Lau], 1
    - [William O. Lau: A woman with a little boy], 2
    - [William O. Lau: Man with a little boy], 3
  - Laurence G. Leavitt, 1952; 59 (Box 1617)
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Laurence G. Leavitt, Headmaster, Vermont Academy], 1
    - [Laurence G. Leavitt: Plaque that reads "This jump was built by the labor and generosity of students and friends of Vermont Academy in memory of Roger Day Emerson 42. 1924 - 1943"], 2
    - [Laurence G. Leavitt: Two men and two women together on snowy hillside], 3
  - Paul Lerman, 1945; 60 (Box 1617)
    - [Paul Lerman: Tow men in uniform in front of lion statue], 1
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Paul Lerman], 2
  - George Kin Leung [color photograph], circa 1957; 61 (Box 1617)
    - [George Kin Leung (color photo): Man dressed in red robes.], 1
    - Note: [letter to Lowell Thomas from George Kin Leung], 2
  - John Libi [includes color photograph], 1961 - 1965; 62 (Box 1617)
    - [John Libi (color photo): Man holding a crate of peaches outside of a market], 1
    - Note[PDF]: [letter 1 to Lowell Thomas from John Libi], 2
    - [John Libi: Man and woman standing in a field wearing hunting outfits, man holding a rifle(?)], 3
    - Note[PDF]: [letter 2 to Lowell Thomas from John Libi], 4
  - Alexander Litchard, 1958; 63 (Box 1617)
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Alexander Litchard], 1
    - [Alexander Litchard:]A view looking south. New lodge will be 1/2 mile to left, 2
    - Verso: A view looking south. New lodge will be 1/2 mile to left, 2-verso
    - [Alexander Litchard:]A N.E. view, duck marsh to left, 3
    - Verso: A N.E. view, duck marsh to left, 3-verso
  - Walt Lockwood, 1961; 64 (Box 1617)
    - [Walt Lockwood:]Caption: USS Burton Island [Boat on icy water], 1
    - Note[PDF]: [outside of Christmas card to Lowell Thomas from Walt Lockwood], 2
    - Note[PDF]: [inside of Christmas card to Lowell Thomas from Walt Lockwood], 3
  - Carl and Laura Lomen [color photograph], 1970; 65 (Box 1617)
    - [Carl and Laura Lomen:]Laura V. Lomen 1970, 1
    - Verso: Laura V. Lomen 1970, 1-verso
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 1 of 2, Carl and Laura Lomen: letter to Lowell Thomas from Mrs. Carl Lomen], 2
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 2 of 2, Carl and Laura Lomen: letter to Lowell Thomas from Mrs. Carl Lomen], 3
  - Captain George William Lyons, Jr., 1948; 66 (Box 1617)
    - [Captain George William Lyons, Jr.:]Caption: Seasons Greetings [Christmas card], 1
    - Note: Alice Margaret Lyons; October 22nd, 1948; Mr. and Mrs. George Wiliam Lyons, Jr., 2
  - Sandra G. Macartney, 1962; 67 (Box 1617)
    - [Sandra G. Macartney: Man putting curlers in woman's hair], 1
    - Note[PDF]: [Sandra G. Macartney: Invitation from Major & Mrs. V. W. Beckhurst], 2
    - Note[PDF]: [Sandra G. Macartney: Page 1 of letter to Lowell Thomas], 3
    - Note[PDF]: [Sandra G. Macartney: Page 2 of letter to Lowell Thomas], 4
  - Phoebe Wann Mackey, 1977; 68 (Box 1617)
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Phoebe Wann Mackey], 1
    - [Phoebe Wann Mackey: Signed cloth], 2
  - L. Stanley Manierre, 1954; 69 (Box 1617)
    - [L. Stanley Manierre: Two men shaking hands][Yukichi Kano], 1
    - Verso: Yukichi Kano
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from L. Stanley Manierre], 2
    - Note[PDF]: [L. Stanley Manierre: newspaper clipping], 3
  - Marine Studios, 1950 - 1951; 70 (Box 1617)
    - Note[PDF]: [Marine Studios: Page 1 of letter to Lowell Thomas regarding Marineland], 1
    - Note[PDF]: [Marine Studios: Page 2 of letter to Lowell Thomas regarding Marineland], 2
    - Note[PDF]: [Marine Studios: Page 3 of letter to Lowell Thomas regarding Marineland], 3
    - [Marine Studios: Porpoise [Dolphin?] jumps through hoop], 4
    - [Marine Studios: Porpoise [Dolphin?] catches ball], 5
    - [Marine Studios: Porpoise [Dolphin?] rings bell], 6
    - [Marine Studios: Porpoise [Dolphin?] jumps through hoop], 7
  - Bill Mark, 1952 - 1969; 71 (Box 1617)
    - Note[PDF]: [letter from Bill Mark to Mary], 1
    - [Bill Mark:]Dear Mary and Lowell, I got the five books. They are perfect. I have my four books in the place of honor atop the book shelf, lording it over some three hundred other biographys&, 2
    - Verso[PDF]: Dear Mary and Lowell, I got the five books. They are perfect. I have my four books in the place of honor atop the book shelf, lording it over some three hundred other biographys&, 2-verso
    - [Bill Mark:]PS I am breaking in a new darkroom printer. I gave her your returned glossy so that she would see just how you wanted it cropped. These are what she came up with&, 3
    - Verso[PDF]: PS I am breaking in a new darkroom printer. I gave her your returned glossy so that she would see just how you wanted it cropped. These are what she came up with&, 3-verso
  - Frank V. Maroney, 1959; 72 (Box 1617)
    - 899 Cripple Creek July 4th Hose Cart Race, 1
    - Verso: 1899 Cripple Creek July 4th Hose Cart Race, 1-verso
    - [Frank V. Maroney:]Caption: Prise Hand Drilling Contest - Victor, Colo. Lehr Foto; Verso: Taken 1911. Victor High School in Bkground. Redlight district in gulch behind fence in Background, 2
    - Verso: Taken 1911. Victor High School in Bkground. Redlight district in gulch behind fence in Background, 2-verso
    - Note: [envelope], 3
  - Elizabeth and Joe Marshall [color photograph], circa 1967; 73 (Box 1617)
    - Joe T. Marshall Sr. and his wife Elizabeth, Laguna Beach, Calif- around 1967, 1
    - Verso: Joe T. Marshall Sr. and his wife Elizabeth, Laguna Beach, Calif- around 1967, 1-verso
    - Note[PDF]: [Elizabeth and Joe Marshall: Page 1 of letter to Lowell Thomas from Elizabeth Marshall], 2
    - Note[PDF]: [Elizabeth and Joe Marshall: Page 2 of letter to Lowell Thomas from Elizabeth Marshall], 3
  - Joe and Joyce Martin, 1974 - 1975; 74 (Box 1617)
    - Note[PDF]: Joe and Joyce Martin: "Name in Lights," Starring Lowell Thomas [front of birthday card to L.T.], 1
    - Note[PDF]: Joe and Joyce Martin: Dear Mr. Thomas- I hope this reaches you in time for your birthday - April 6th& [inside of birthday card to L.T.], 2
    - Note[PDF]: Joe and Joyce Martin: Martin Enterprises & Associates [back of birthday card to L.T.], 3
    - [Joe and Joyce Martin: Executive Productions sign that reads "Happy Birthday"][Happy Birthday sign], 4
  - Mrs. Robert N. McKee [color photographs], 1963; 75 (Box 1617)
    - [Mrs. Robert N. McKee (color photo): Two vases on table and plate mounted on the wall], 1
    - [Mrs. Robert N. McKee (color photo): Two vases on table and plate mounted on the wall], 2
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 1 of letter to Lowell Thomas from Mrs. Robert N. McKee], 3
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 2 of letter to Lowell Thomas from Mrs. Robert N. McKee], 4
  - Harry H. Mead, 1957; 76 (Box 1617)
    - [Harry H. Mead: Man and woman standing together][Image that was attached to front of card], 1
    - Note: Seasons Greetings, from the Philippines, 2
    - Note[PDF]: [inside of card - letter to Lowell Thomas from Harry H. Mead, 3
  - Harold Meixell, 1954; 77 (Box 1617)
    - [Harold Meixell:]This group from Ashland, Ohio caught on hook and line 15 blaack sturgeon on the Goulair River just a short distance from Lake Superior, in 1953&, 1
    - Verso: This group from Ashland, Ohio caught on hook and line 15 blaack sturgeon on the Goulair River just a short distance from Lake Superior, in 1953&, 1-verso
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Harold Meixell, 2
  - George T. Miller, 1969; 78 (Box 1617)
    - [George T. Miller:]Official Portrait--Lieutenant General Lewis W. Walt, 05436, USMC, (winter services, uncovered)., 1
    - Verso: Official Portrait--Lieutenant General Lewis W. Walt, 05436, USMC, (winter services, uncovered)., 1-verso
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from George T. Miller], 2
  - Beaufort Mooramong, 1956 - 1963; 79 (Box 1617)
    - [Beaufort Mooramong:]1956 Olympics, Donald, Baroness Rhyklrunder[?], Baron Otto Rhylrunder (famous Swedish fencer) Mrs. Neil Ramsay Saunders, my father Stanley Addams Morramong, 1
    - Verso: 1956 Olympics, Donald, Baroness Rhyklrunder[?], Baron Otto Rhylrunder (famous Swedish fencer) Mrs. Neil Ramsay Saunders, my father Stanley Addams Morramong, 1-verso
    - [Beaufort Mooramong:]1958, Baron + Baroness Otto Rhybrunder[?] Otto-Sammie; with my small poodle Mitze (now dead), with giant poodle Rags, our pool - Morramong, 2
    - Verso: 1958, Baron + Baroness Otto Rhybrunder[?] Otto-Sammie; with my small poodle Mitze (now dead), with giant poodle Rags, our pool - Morramong, 2-verso
    - [Beaufort Mooramong:]Taken in March 1963; Claire Mackennan - Taken in back garden of town house 220 Domain Rd. South Garra, Melbourne, 3
    - Verso: Taken in March 1963; Claire Mackennan - Taken in back garden of town house 220 Domain Rd. South Garra, Melbourne, 3-verso
    - Note[PDF]: Beaufort Mooramong [Front of letter to Lowell Thomas], 4
    - Note[PDF]: Beaufort Mooramong: [Inside of letter to Lowell Thomas], 5
    - Note[PDF]: Beaufort Mooramong [Back of letter to Lowell Thomas], 6
  - Don Mozley, 1966; 80 (Box 1617)
    - [Don Mozley:]Home of Lawrence of Arabia, 1
    - Verso: Home of Lawrence of Arabia, 1-verso
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Don S. Mozley, Sr. concerning the birthplace of Lawrenceof Arabia], 2
  Box 1618
- Topical files 2, 2.1.9.5
  - Naomi Murray and Richard "Dick"& Seldon, 1962; 1 (Box 1618)
    - [Richard "Dick"& Seldon], 1
    - [Naomi Murray], 2
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 1 of letter to Lowell Thomas from (Dick) R. Sheldon Murray & Naomi], 3
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 2 of letter to Lowell Thomas from (Dick) R. Sheldon Murray & Naomi], 4
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 3 of letter to Lowell Thomas from (Dick) R. Sheldon Murray & Naomi], 5
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 4 of letter to Lowell Thomas from (Dick) R. Sheldon Murray & Naomi], 6
  - M - miscellaneous, 1939 - circa 1954; 2 (Box 1618)
    - [M - miscellaneous: Two men and two women stadnign together in front of two cakes], 1
    - [M - miscellaneous: Man standing in front of building] Caption: Cordially Yours, Nums Jordy, 2
    - [M - miscellaneous: Little girl with hat and hand muff] Feb. 6-1939, 3
    - Verso: Feb. 6-1939, 3-verso
  - Carlton S. Nash, 1953 - 1957; 3 (Box 1618)
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Carlton S. Nash of Nash Dinosaurland, 1
    - [Carlton S. Nash: Entrance to house], 2
    - [Carlton S. Nash: Lady working on stepping stones, 3
    - [Carlton S. Nash: Stepping stones with dinosaur "foot" prints], 4
  - Donald W. Nass [includes photographs of Lowell Thomas] [color photographs], 1979 - 1980; 4 (Box 1618)
    - [Donald W. Nass: Lowell Thomas standing between a man and a woman], 1
    - [Donald W. Nass: Lowell Thomas standing next to a man], 2
    - Note[PDF]: Donald W. Nass: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Donald, Joyce + Bill Nass], 3
  - Captain Harry Newak [includes photographs of Lowell Thomas], 1974 - 1980; 5 (Box 1618)
    - Note[PDF]: Captain Harry Newark: [letter to Lowell Thomas from The Marine Society of the City of New York], 1
    - [Captain Harry Newark:] April 11 1977 [Lowell Thomas speaking at a podium, banner that is hanging over crowd that reads "Marine Society of the City of New York Chartered 1770"], 2
    - Verso: April 11 1977, 2-verso
    - [Captain Harry Newark:] V-Adm James Coluent USN; Capt Hoeuesh [?] Marine Society City of NY, April 11, 1977 Plaza NYC, 3
    - Verso: V-Adm James Coluent USN; Capt Hoeuesh [?] Marine Society City of NY, April 11, 1977 Plaza NYC, 3-verso
  - William G. O'Brien, 1948 - 1954; 6 (Box 1618)
    - [William G. O'Brien:]New York - July 5/ 1954 presentation [?] - as wind up of his U.S. Tom. Which we made&.[Three men standing together], 1
    - Verso: New York - July 5/ 1954 presentation [?] - as wind up of his U.S. Tom. Which we made&., 1-verso
    - [William G. O'Brien: Man playing tennis]Cannes - Aug 1948, 2
    - Verso: Cannes - Aug 1948, 2-verso
    - [William G. O'Brien: Man walking in Rome]Rome 1952, 3
    - Verso: Rome 1952, 3-verso
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from William G. O'Brien], 4
  - Oscar F. Olson, 1957; 7 (Box 1618)
    - [Oscar F. Olson: Portrait of a man], 1
    - Note: [Page 1 of letter to Lowell Thomas from Oscar F. Olson, 2
    - Note: [Page 2 of letter to Lowell Thomas from Oscar F. Olson, 3
  - Parker Pen Company, 1953; 8 (Box 1618)
    - [Parker Pen Company: Shadow boxes holding pens], 1
    - [Parker Pen Company: People observing the pens of famous people ], 2
  - D. C. Paschke, 1947; 9 (Box 1618)
    - [D.C. Paschke: Caption: Mums by Pashke. Cars parked on the side of the road, people picking up mums.], 1
    - [D.C. Paschke: People gathered around mums. Sign that reads "Fulton Lewis, Jr. The New Chrysanthemum"], 2
    - Verso: Photos by Schubeck North East, Penna., 2-verso
  - Pawling, New York (Frances Graber) [includes photographs of Lowell Thomas], circa 1939; 10 (Box 1618)
    - [Pawling, New York (Frances Graber): Men standing together, Lowell Thomas center], 1
    - [Pawling, New York (Frances Graber):]Carroll Vacation 1939; Aug 5 - '39, 2
    - Verso: Carroll Vacation 1939; Aug 5 - '39, 2-verso
    - [Pawling, New York (Frances Graber): Three men standing together. Police officer at left, Lowell Thomas at right], 3
    - [Pawling, New York (Frances Grabler): Group of men together on a baseball field for a picture], 4
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Mrs. Hogan from Francis Graber, 5
  - Edward Payne, 1943; 11 (Box 1618)
    - [Edward Payne: Looking out of a window], 1
    - [Edward Payne: Dogs on snowy lawn], 2
  - Harry Raymond Pierce, 1952; 12 (Box 1618)
    - [Harry Raymond Pierce:]Caption: Scene on Ford Quadrangle, 1
  - Olive Nagel Porter, 1963; 13 (Box 1618)
    - [Olive Nagel Porter:]Caption: Rufus Porter; Old[?] Nagel Porter [sign: Yonder is Cripple Creek], 1
  - The Potter School [color photographs], 1963; 14 (Box 1618)
    - [The Potter School (color photo): Lowell Thomas on skiis with a woman], 1
    - [The Potter School (color photo): People on skiis], 2
  - Robert W. Pottschmidt [color photograph], 1980; 15 (Box 1618)
    - [Robert W. Pottschmidt (color photo): Close-up of a man], 1
  - R. P. Probasco, 1938; 16 (Box 1618)
    - [R.P. Probasco: Profile of man in hat and glasses]"Old Pro" 7/5/88, 1
    - Verso: "Old Pro" 7/5/88 [38?], 1-verso
  - Private James Norman Richardson, circa 1945; 17 (Box 1618)
    - Pvt. James Norman Richardson; CoE - 87th Mt. Inf.; A.P.O. 309 Fort Lewis; Tacoma Washington, 1
    - Verso: Pvt. James Norman Richardson; CoE - 87th Mt. Inf.; A.P.O. 309 Fort Lewis; Tacoma Washington, 1-verso
  - M. Ritu Rana, 1968; 18 (Box 1618)
    - [M. Ritu Rana: People walking around a city], 1
    - Verso: Andhra Bank, 1-verso
    - [M. Ritu Rana: Palace (?)], 2
    - Verso: (Audhra Pradesh) Assembly, 2-verso
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 1 of letter to Lowell Thomas from M. Ritu Rana], 3
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 2 of letter to Lowell Thomas from M. Ritu Rana], 4
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 3 of letter to Lowell Thomas from M. Ritu Rana], 5
  - Walter Orr Roberts, 1965; 19 (Box 1618)
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 1 of letter to Lowell Thomas from Walter Orr Roberts], 1
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 2 of letter to Lowell Thomas from Walter Orr Roberts], 2
    - [Walter Orr Roberts: Aerial view of land][Nov 29 1965], 3
    - Verso: Nov 29 1965, 3-verso
    - [Walter Orr Roberts: Aerial view of land][Nov 29 1965], 4
    - Verso: Nov 29 1965, 4-verso
    - [Walter Orr Roberts: Rolling hills][Nov 29 1965], 5
    - Verso: Nov 29 1965, 5-verso
    - [Walter Orr Roberts: Aerial view of land - mountains, large estate][Nov 29 1965], 6
    - Verso: Nov 29 1965, 6-verso
  - Fred R. Robinson, 1955; 20 (Box 1618)
    - [Fred R. Robinson: Man holding shot deer], 1
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Fred R. Robinson], 2
  - Nelson Rockefeller, 1973; 21 (Box 1618)
    - [Nelson Rockefeller: Lady on skiis]Caption: [semi-legible], 1
  - Louis A. Romanet, "Kabluk of the Eskimo", 1944; 22 (Box 1618)
    - [Louis A. Romanet:]A lady from the land where people never grow old. - This is Mrs. Kabluk Romanov[?] of whom you speak in the book "Kabbuk of the Eskimo." She is 54 in the [?] this spring. 7 kids, married 37 years and a real add to the [?] and Kabluk's fair treatment, 1
    - Verso: A lady from the land where people never grow old. - This is Mrs. Kabluk Romanov[?] of whom you speak in the book "Kabbuk of the Eskimo." She is 54 in the [?] this spring. 7 kids, married 37 years and a real add to the [?] and Kabluk's fair treatment, 1-verso
    - [Louis A. Romanet:]Kabluk at 64, and not over the hill yet. May/10/44, 2
    - Verso: Kabluk at 64, and not over the hill yet. May/10/44, 2-verso
  - Harold Salisbury, 1966; 23 (Box 1618)
    - [Harold Salisbury: Three women and one man standing on sidewalk], 1
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 1 of First letter to Lowell Thomas from Harold Salisbury], 2